interactive rebase in progress; onto a99a082
Last commands done (2 commands done):
   pick fbac6d4 fix: finalize conflict resolution in rag-service main.py
   pick 2d5af71 fix: finalize conflict resolution in rag-service main.py
No commands remaining.
You are currently editing a commit while rebasing branch 'feature/ccc-response-format' on 'a99a082'.
  (use "git commit --amend" to amend the current commit)
  (use "git rebase --continue" once you are satisfied with your changes)

Untracked files:
  (use "git add <file>..." to include in what will be committed)
	git_status.txt

nothing added to commit but untracked files present (use "git add" to track)
